contextures.com 2019-03-11

# Contextures Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Contextures website, owned by Contextures Inc., which is located in Canada. The site is hosted on servers owned by Arvixe, which is located in the USA. We respect and protect the privacy of our users. This privacy policy tells you how we collect and use information.

The term "Personal Information" in this privacy policy means any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained. We do not collect Personal Information about you when you visit this online service.

### Scope

The purpose of this website is to provide you with trusted information about using Microsoft Excel.

### Personal information

If you contact us we will collect the email address, and any other identifying information you provide, such as a name or phone number. Please do not give us other personal or sensitive information.

### Website analytics

This site does not collect any data from visitors, other than standard server logs. However, to improve your experience on our site, we may use 'cookies' -- a cookie is a small text file that a site may place on your computer as a tool to remember your preferences. Cookies are an industry standard and most major web sites use them. 

You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.

Our website may contain links to other websites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites, so when you go to other websites from here, be aware and read their privacy policy.

Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.

By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner described in [Google's Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/) and for the purposes set out above. You can opt out of Google Analytics if you disable or refuse the cookie, disable JavaScript, or use the [opt-out service provided by Google](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

### Advertising

Also, this site does use third-party advertising companies, including Google and Amazon, to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. 

These advertisers may use cookies which are collected by the advertising companies. For more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please check the advertisers' websites for respective privacy policies. 

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to this website or other websites.
  * Google's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to this site, and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), or by visiting the [About Ads opt out page](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

### Subscriptions

If you sign up for my Excel newsletter, your name and email address are collected, and securely stored, by AWeber. You can use the link at the bottom of any email, to immediately unsubscribe from the mailing list. Emails will no longer be sent to you, and your information will be deleted from the mailing list. 

If you purchase Contextures' Excel products, the transaction is managed through the secure e-junkie.com website. The payment is processed through PayPal, and they do not share your credit card details with me, or with e-junkie. PayPal only notifies us that your payment has been completed, so that the product can be sent to you., and product support can be provided, if required

If you subscribe to my RSS Feeds or Email Updates (powered by Feedburner), I ask for contact information such as name and email address. You may opt-out of these communications at any time. Your personal information will never be sold or given to a third party, and you will never be spammed by me. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns please contact Debra Dalgleish at ddalgleish @ contextures.com 

Privacy policy dated May 2018.
